<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Partners on Duyan Technologies</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/</link><description>Recent content in Partners on Duyan Technologies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More Than a Telecom Master Agent</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p1/</guid><description>Since 2014, our award-winning team has helped businesses streamline the selection, implementation, and ongoing management of IT &amp;amp; Telecom Infrastructures.
Through our expertise in cloud contact center and extensive relationships with carriers, we are able to navigate the seemingly infinite number of available IT and Network Service offerings and recommend the most efficient Voice, Data, and Cloud solutions to meet the needs of our clients.
And with offices in US and China, we are able to serve businesses in a broad geographical area.</description></item><item><title>Product Engagements</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p2/</guid><description>Our cloud-ready, multi-tenants, and production-grade products are ready for your business. You can engage in our SaaS (Software as a Service) Offer, On-premises Offer, White-labelling Offer, and Full Technology Offer.
SaaS Offer Our cloud-based, multi-tenants SaaS Offer is a full featured solution with continue platform upgrade and support by our technical team. Partners of Our SaaS Offer can “resell” or directly “use” the solution on your business. For “reselling” the solution you can charge your clients with setup, consulting, or training fees.</description></item><item><title>Service Engagements</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p3/</guid><description>Our strong, cost-effective technical team is ready for various level of service engagements including Consultation Offer, Integration Offer, Customization Offer, and Outsourcing/Offshoring Offer.
Consultation Offer Our technology consultation offer is rooted on our deep knowledge in our product domain and experiences of servicing our customers with the products. We can bring an objective solution to the table and help your business with the best practice to improve productivity and efficiency while reducing costs.</description></item></channel></rss>