<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Duyan Technologies</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/</link><description>Recent content on Duyan Technologies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://duyantechnologies.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Managed Services Provider</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/managedprovider/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/managedprovider/</guid><description>Managed Services will extend and enhance your IT and business functionality while enabling greater IT agility and scalability.
With unparalleled industry expertise and decades of experience, Duyan customers and partners receive a level of knowledge and support that exceeds all expectations.
Move the vital day-to-day operations of elements of your IT infrastructure to proven industry experts. Managed Services assumes responsibility for the key tasks of installation, configuration, and management of critical applications and infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>A Master Agency</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/masteragency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/masteragency/</guid><description>A master agent is an organization contracted with telecom providers to facilitate business on their behalf. Duyan takes a unique approach to this business model by placing its focus on customer and partner advocacy.
With deeply entrenched relationships with he three big carriers in China — China Telecom, China Unicom, and China Mobile, as well as the MII (Ministry of Information Industry), Duyan uniquely supports our direct customers and partners to engage in opening or extending services nationally and internationally, giving customers and partners a competitive edge in the marketplace.</description></item><item><title>A Trusted Advisor</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/trustedadvisor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/trustedadvisor/</guid><description>As a trusted advisor of our customers and partners, Duyan can take all the pain from the process so all you need to do is make an informed decision.
It’s a full time job to keep abreast of nascent technologies, best practices and compliance. It’s also a full time job to determine the right solution architecture, evaluate service providers, negotiate agreements, and implement a deployment. Chances are, it’s just not your full time job.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/cloud/</guid><description>Public, Private and Hybrid Cloud services are evolving and maturing at an increasing rate. Which one is right for your business? Our &amp;lsquo;3 Steps to Cloud&amp;rsquo; approach (Advisory, Sourcing, and Management) will help you see the Cloud’s greatest benefits.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/connectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/connectivity/</guid><description>Whether you are connecting to the Internet, a data center, or other corporate locations, Duyan will help you evaluate all available connectivity options.
Our international end-to-end connectivity services include:
The procurement and implementation of the three connection segments: International connection between China and the destination country; Local extension nationwide in China; Local extension in the destination country. End-to-end connectivity arrangement, testing, and maintenance. Manage the settlement with the carriers of the destination country.</description></item><item><title>Data Center Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/datacenter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/datacenter/</guid><description>Today’s data centers are much more than just space and power. They are purpose-built facilities designed to support all of your demanding colocation, hosting, compliance and connectivity requirements.</description></item><item><title>Managed Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/managed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/managed/</guid><description>Move the vital day-to-day operations of elements of your IT infrastructure to proven industry experts. Managed Services will enhance your IT and business functionality, while enabling greater IT agility and scalability.</description></item><item><title>More Than a Telecom Master Agent</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p1/</guid><description>Since 2014, our award-winning team has helped businesses streamline the selection, implementation, and ongoing management of IT &amp;amp; Telecom Infrastructures.
Through our expertise in cloud contact center and extensive relationships with carriers, we are able to navigate the seemingly infinite number of available IT and Network Service offerings and recommend the most efficient Voice, Data, and Cloud solutions to meet the needs of our clients.
And with offices in US and China, we are able to serve businesses in a broad geographical area.</description></item><item><title>Powering business success with technology</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/about/p1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/about/p1/</guid><description>Bringing together experienced Cloud IT Specialists and Master Agent Networks, Duyan is the first-of-its-kind, channel-led, one-stop-shop for technology services.
Duyan offers the digital transformation expertise of top channel leaders, best-in-class technology that&amp;rsquo;s purpose-built for you, and the most diverse catalog of solutions, giving customers one touchpoint for every business technology need, including cloud, voice, connectivity, IoT, services and support.</description></item><item><title>Product Engagements</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p2/</guid><description>Our cloud-ready, multi-tenants, and production-grade products are ready for your business. You can engage in our SaaS (Software as a Service) Offer, On-premises Offer, White-labelling Offer, and Full Technology Offer.
SaaS Offer Our cloud-based, multi-tenants SaaS Offer is a full featured solution with continue platform upgrade and support by our technical team. Partners of Our SaaS Offer can “resell” or directly “use” the solution on your business. For “reselling” the solution you can charge your clients with setup, consulting, or training fees.</description></item><item><title>SaaS Contact Center Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/saas/</guid><description>Our SaaS (Software as a Service) Contact Center service in China is a cloud-based, multi-tenants offer for clients who need voice and SMS communication service in China.
Due to strict spam monitoring and regulations on telco service terminating in China, service providers outside of the country hardly get proper access. Our service fully comply with the regulations of The Ministry of Industry and Information Technology of People’s Republic of China and can meet your specific needs.</description></item><item><title>Service Engagements</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/partners/p3/</guid><description>Our strong, cost-effective technical team is ready for various level of service engagements including Consultation Offer, Integration Offer, Customization Offer, and Outsourcing/Offshoring Offer.
Consultation Offer Our technology consultation offer is rooted on our deep knowledge in our product domain and experiences of servicing our customers with the products. We can bring an objective solution to the table and help your business with the best practice to improve productivity and efficiency while reducing costs.</description></item><item><title>Technology Solution Consulting Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/consulting/</guid><description>Through our vast experience and wealth of IT industry knowledge, Duyan will identify the solution you are looking for. Through technology evaluation, selection, design, and implementation, Duyan ensures that the solution you select meets both your needs and your budget.
Architecture and Design Duyan is rooted in design, develop, and operate a SaaS contact center platform that currently supports thousands of seats and concurrent calls. We understand that assessing needs and mapping them to projected growth is the foundation for creating scalable environments that drive success.</description></item><item><title>Your One Stop Source</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/about/p2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/about/p2/</guid><description>Bringing together experienced Cloud IT Specialists and Master Agent Networks, Duyan is the first-of-its-kind, channel-led, one-stop-shop for technology services.
Duyan offers the digital transformation expertise of top channel leaders, best-in-class technology that&amp;rsquo;s purpose-built for you, and the most diverse catalog of solutions, giving customers one touchpoint for every business technology need, including cloud, voice, connectivity, IoT, services and support.</description></item></channel></rss>