<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Duyan Technologies</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/</link><description>Recent content on Duyan Technologies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://duyantechnologies.com/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Managed Services Provider</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/managedprovider/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/managedprovider/</guid><description>Managed Services will extend and enhance your IT and business functionality while enabling greater IT agility and scalability.
With unparalleled industry expertise and decades of experience, Duyan customers and partners receive a level of knowledge and support that exceeds all expectations.
Move the vital day-to-day operations of elements of your IT infrastructure to proven industry experts. Managed Services assumes responsibility for the key tasks of installation, configuration, and management of critical applications and infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>A Master Agency</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/masteragency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/masteragency/</guid><description>A master agent is an organization contracted with telecom providers to facilitate business on their behalf. Duyan takes a unique approach to this business model by placing its focus on customer and partner advocacy.
With deeply entrenched relationships with he three big carriers in China — China Telecom, China Unicom, and China Mobile, as well as the MII (Ministry of Information Industry), Duyan uniquely supports our direct customers and partners to engage in opening or extending services nationally and internationally, giving customers and partners a competitive edge in the marketplace.</description></item><item><title>A Trusted Advisor</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/trustedadvisor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/home/trustedadvisor/</guid><description>As a trusted advisor of our customers and partners, Duyan can take all the pain from the process so all you need to do is make an informed decision.
It’s a full time job to keep abreast of nascent technologies, best practices and compliance. It’s also a full time job to determine the right solution architecture, evaluate service providers, negotiate agreements, and implement a deployment. Chances are, it’s just not your full time job.</description></item></channel></rss>