<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on Duyan Technologies</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on Duyan Technologies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://duyantechnologies.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/cloud/</guid><description>Public, Private and Hybrid Cloud services are evolving and maturing at an increasing rate. Which one is right for your business? Our &amp;lsquo;3 Steps to Cloud&amp;rsquo; approach (Advisory, Sourcing, and Management) will help you see the Cloud’s greatest benefits.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/connectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/connectivity/</guid><description>Whether you are connecting to the Internet, a data center, or other corporate locations, Duyan will help you evaluate all available connectivity options.
Our international end-to-end connectivity services include:
The procurement and implementation of the three connection segments: International connection between China and the destination country; Local extension nationwide in China; Local extension in the destination country. End-to-end connectivity arrangement, testing, and maintenance. Manage the settlement with the carriers of the destination country.</description></item><item><title>Data Center Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/datacenter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/datacenter/</guid><description>Today’s data centers are much more than just space and power. They are purpose-built facilities designed to support all of your demanding colocation, hosting, compliance and connectivity requirements.</description></item><item><title>Managed Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/managed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/managed/</guid><description>Move the vital day-to-day operations of elements of your IT infrastructure to proven industry experts. Managed Services will enhance your IT and business functionality, while enabling greater IT agility and scalability.</description></item><item><title>SaaS Contact Center Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/saas/</guid><description>Our SaaS (Software as a Service) Contact Center service in China is a cloud-based, multi-tenants offer for clients who need voice and SMS communication service in China.
Due to strict spam monitoring and regulations on telco service terminating in China, service providers outside of the country hardly get proper access. Our service fully comply with the regulations of The Ministry of Industry and Information Technology of People’s Republic of China and can meet your specific needs.</description></item><item><title>Technology Solution Consulting Service</title><link>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://duyantechnologies.com/services/consulting/</guid><description>Through our vast experience and wealth of IT industry knowledge, Duyan will identify the solution you are looking for. Through technology evaluation, selection, design, and implementation, Duyan ensures that the solution you select meets both your needs and your budget.
Architecture and Design Duyan is rooted in design, develop, and operate a SaaS contact center platform that currently supports thousands of seats and concurrent calls. We understand that assessing needs and mapping them to projected growth is the foundation for creating scalable environments that drive success.</description></item></channel></rss>